{
    "id": "dee320197efe4380a0acf226b837d3fd",
    "title": "Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Iron ………………….. in many countries.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "find",
                "found",
                "is found"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He wondered how ………………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "it is made",
                "was it made",
                "it was made"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The university ………………… in",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was found",
                "was founded",
                "found"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You can …………………… this.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "avail",
                "avail of",
                "avail yourself of"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He was ………………….. sorry.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "very",
                "very much",
                "much"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He was …………………. to invite me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "very kind",
                "very kind enough",
                "kind enough"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He told the story …………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in details",
                "in detail",
                "with details"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………. there was no one there.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Before long",
                "Long before",
                "Long ago"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "This book is ………….. interesting.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "very",
                "too",
                "very much"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "……………… such a sight.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Never I have seen",
                "Never have I seen",
                "Never I saw"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}